# 哒 哒 哒吧哒 哒 哒 吧哒吧哒吧 #
Da, da, da-ba-da, da, da, ba-da-ba-da-ba
翻译
Yata熊
# 哒 哒 哒吧哒 哒 哒 我们走 #
Da, da, da-ba-da, da, da let's go!
翻译
VK熊
# 我们同在 #
We'll be there
# 一个眼神 一个微笑 一声赞许 如往常一样 #
A wink and a smile and a great old time
Fantopia
翻托邦
校对
VK熊
# 我们同在 #
Yeah, we'll be there
# 无论身处何处 快乐永远同在 #
Wherever we are, there's some fun to be found
翻托邦
Fantopia
后期
VK熊
# 转过街角 我们同在 #
We'll be there when you turn that corner
# 跳出树丛 #
We'll jump out the bush
特效
土皮熊
# 带着大大的熊笑 #
With a big bear hug and a smile
# 我们同在 #
We'll be there
三贱客
熊熊
圣诞派对
- 该死 - 嘿 棕熊
- Dang it! - Hey, Grizz.
你想来点素食酒吗
Do you want some vegan nog?
没加鸡蛋 但加了双倍的酒
None of the eggs, but, uh, twice the nog!
不 不用了
Mmm, nah, I'm good.
来了 来了
I'm coming. Coming!
兄弟 你没事吧
Whoa! Bro, you okay?
白熊找到了完美的树
Ice Bear found perfect tree.
你不觉得它有点大吗
Don't you think it's a little big?
白熊的座右铭 "要么不要 要么最大"
Ice Bear's motto, "Go big, or go home."
你好 熊熊们 希望你们有个快乐的平安夜
Hello there, bears! Hope you're having a lovely Christmas eve.
你们有一些邮件
I have some mail for you!
好了 接着
Ow! All right, here ya go!
谢谢你 节日快乐
Thank you! Happy holidays!
没事 有一个... 哎哟... 快乐的一天
No problem. Have a... ouch... lovely day!
让我看看...
Now, let's see...
- 是什么啊 - 白熊希望是优惠券
- What is it?! - Ice Bear hopes it's coupons.
伙计们 过来看看
Guys, guys guys... Come check it out!
我们得到了 不是一张 也不是两张
We just got, not one, not two,
而是三张今晚的圣诞派对邀请
but three Christmas party invitations for tonight!
多么好的朋友们啊
Ha! What a great bunch of friends!
这是首个圣诞节 我们不用闲坐着吃东西
This'll be the first Christmas we'll have stuff to do
而是有派对可以参加
other than sit around and eat!
白熊很感谢
Ice Bear grateful.
电子邮件
Ooh, an e-mail.
什么 我们怎么会收到糯懦拉的电子邮件
Ughh, what?! Why are we getting e-mails from Nom Nom?
我不知道 看看吧
I don't know. Let's check it out.
这是欢乐的季节...
'Tis the season to be jolly...
就在糯懦拉的疯狂节日聚会
at Nom Nom's insane holiday bash!
都是你最爱的名人 最精致的美食
All your favorite celebs, the finest gourmet food,
还有海量免费礼物 糯懦拉的圣诞狂欢
and tons of free swag! Nom Nom's Christmas rager!
你来吗
Are you in?
天哪 那派对看起来很不错啊 对吧
Gee, that seems like a pretty neat party, huh?
没错 太惨了 我们今晚太忙了
Yeah, too bad we're so busy tonight, right?
在你们想着不来之前
And, before you think twice about not coming,
每位客人都将获得免费小狗
free puppy for every guest!
无法拒绝这可爱的脸吧
Can't say no to that face!
没错 无法拒绝
He's right, I can't.
我们得去参加啊 兄弟们
Aah! We got to go to this thing, you guys.
但我们怎么才能一个不落呢
But how will we have time to go to all these parties?
我想 如果我们花少一点时间
Well, I think, I mean, if we spend just a little less time
在其他派对上 就能在今夜结束前
at these other parties, we'll be able to end the night
去糯懦拉的派对... 还能和所有人见一面
at Nom Nom's party... and we can still see everybody!
你觉得我们能成功吗
Do you think we can pull that off?
当然 就是简单的计时而已
Of course. It's simple math!
好吧 我设一下闹钟 这样就不会迟了
Okay! Well, I'll set alarms so we can keep on schedule.
圣诞狂欢
Christmas rager!
好了 记住 我们按计划进行
Okay, remember, we stick to the plan.
时间一到 我们就得走
When the alarm goes off, we gotta leave.
明白
Got it.
你们来了 刚刚好
You're here! And just in time!
进来吧
Come on in!
希望你们准备好了... 圣诞派对总部
I hope you're ready for... Christmas Party Central!
这派对太疯狂了
This party's pretty crazy.
你们来了就热闹了
It will be now that you're here!
但我想首先 我们先玩下腰吧
But I thought for starters, we could try limbo!
下腰 谁来
Whoo! Yeah, limbo! Who's in?!
棒 你做到了
Yay! You did it!
我不知道该做什么
Ughh! I don't know what to do!
是不是以我的能量水平 要求别人还不够格
Is it so much to ask for someone with my level of energy?
我觉得没人能跟你相比了 游骑兵
Oh, I don't think anyone can match your level, Tabes.
别担心 我们来帮你
But don't worry, we got you covered.
- 胖胖 - 明白
- Pan Pan? - On it.
让我们动起来
Whoa, hoo, whoo! Let's get movin'!
- 来吧 - 好的
- Come on! - Yeah!
好了 既然我们都来了 鼓个掌
Okay, now that we're all up, clap those hands!
来吧
Come on, now!
好了 就这样 很简单
All right, there it is! It's easy!
移动脚步 下腰走过这跟杆子
Just move your feet and wiggle on down to the limbo beat!
好吧 谁还能再低一点
All right, who thinks they can go lower?!
棕熊 我们得走了
Hey, Grizz, we gotta go!
游骑兵 抱歉 这很有趣
Well, Tabes, sorry, this was fun,
但我们得走了 谢谢
but we gotta be somewhere else. Thanks!
伙计们 等等 你们不能走...
Guys, wait! You can't go yet...
- 派对才刚开始 - 抱歉... 没时间
- The party just got started! - Sorry... no time.
这真是太棒了
It's been a jolly wonderful, uh, thing.
圣诞快乐 再见
Merry Christmas, bye!
等等 邀请函上面说了去哪
Wait, where did the invitation say to go again?
地图上画着一棵树 或者...
Well, the map points to a big tree, I think, or...
就是这棵了
Oh. This has to be it.
但如果这是派对 查理去哪了
But if this is the party, then where's Charlie?
你们好 朋友们
Hola, amigos!
圣诞快乐
Feliz navidad!
快上来 派对在里面
Come on up, the party's inside!
我不知道自己还能爬多高
I don't know how much higher I can climb.
帮帮我
Help me!
你们爬上来了
Hey, hey, you made it!
查理 为什么你的派对在树里
Uh, Charlie, why is your party in a tree?
圣诞派对必须在
Well, you have to have a Christmas party
圣诞树里 笨蛋 所有人都知道
in a Christmas tree, silly! Everyone knows that.
- 我觉得不对 - 当然是对的
- I don't think that's right. - Of course it is!
看看 我有所有的传统圣诞元素
Just look, I got all the traditional festivities!
圣诞卡...
Christmas cards...
小心地挂着袜子
stockings hung with care...
rain deer
驯鹿
reindeer.
当然 如果你们饿了
And, of course, if you're hungry,
我还有糖果
I got all the confection essentials.
蛋酒
Oh, heh heh, eggnog.
我差点忘了火鸡了
Oh, I almost forgot to check on the turkey!
嗨 火鸡 怎么样了
Hey, turkey, how's it going?!
好吧
Ha, all right!
你们来得很是时候
You know, you guys actually just came in time.
我需要你们帮我 找一颗星星挂在树顶
I could use your help finding a star to put on top of the tree.
奶盒
Milk carton?
不对
Nope.
- 这个怎么样 - 那不是星星
- What do you guys think? - That's not a star.
星星是尖的 而且是星形
A star is, you know, pointy and star-shaped.
闹钟响了
Oh, the alarm went off.
抱歉 我们得走了 查理
Sorry, we gotta get going, Charlie.
祝你找到合适的星星
Uh, good luck finding the right star for your tree, though.
但是我希望你们能帮我挑一颗
But I want you guys to help me choose it.
谢谢你的蛋酒
Thanks for eggnog.
不客气
You're welcome.
天啊 我们能在克洛伊家的时间更少了
Oh, man, we have even less time at Chloe's.
爬树花了太多时间
We spent too much time climbing down that tree.
嗨 伙计们 欢迎
Hey, guys! Welcome!
快进来
Come on in!
谢谢
Thank you.
这边请 先生们
Right this way, sirs.
这是我的家人
Meet my family members, guys.
- 你们好 - 你们好
- Hi. - Oh, hello.
哇 它们是真的熊啊
Whoa! They're real bears!
熊熊们你们好
Oh, hi, bears!
熊熊们好啊 请随便一点
Hi, bears! Make yourselves at home!
快看看这些好吃的
Check out all the food, guys!
妈妈和我从昨天就开始准备这顿晚餐了
Mom and I have been working on this dinner since yesterday.
这看上去太棒了
This looks amazing, man.
我真希望能留下吃晚餐
I really wish we could've stayed for dinner.
你们当然要留下啦
Of course you're staying for dinner!
- 来 坐下吧 - 但是... 但是...
- Come on, sit! - But... but...
我们应该还有一点时间吧
We still have a bit of time?
谢谢你们的热情款待
Thank you for your hospitality, everyone.
哎呀 对不起
Oops, sorry.
不好意思
Excuse us.
你们块头真大
Ha! You guys are huge!
- 约翰 小声点 - 不 你才小声点
- John, be quiet! - No, you be quiet!
别管我的表弟
Ugh! Just ignore my cousin.
好了 我们开始开动吧
All right! We should start.
天啊 看上去都这么好吃
Oh, wow. This all looks amazing!
白熊来到了韩国圣诞天堂
Ice Bear is in Korean Christmas heaven.
糟糕
Oh, no!
闹钟响了 对不起 帕克先生
There goes our alarm. I'm sorry, Mrs. Park,
但是我们得走了
but we have to head out.
别开玩笑了 你们才刚来
Don't be ridiculous, you just got here!
对不起 克洛伊 我们真留不下了
I'm sorry, Chloe, we can't. Ow!
也尝尝这个小饼
Oh, try these, too. This is called jeon.
喂
Hey.
小海豹尝起来什么味道啊
What do baby seals taste like?
啊 不不不不不
Oh, no, no, no, no, no!
- 我是个素食者 - 没错
- I'm a vegetarian. - Yes.
这个你肯定很喜欢
Oh, and this one you'll really like.
好吃吧
What do you think?
这个很难出鲜味 但是...
It's really hard to get the umami flavor, but...
什么
Huh?!
好了 这个确实很好吃 克洛伊
Okay, that was really good, Chloe,
但我们真的要走了
but we really have to go now.
我们把这些打包走
We'll take these to go,
然后告诉你好不好吃 怎么样
and we'll let you know how we feel about the food, yeah?
哎呀 太对不起了
Whoa! I'm so, so, so so sorry!
我们不是故意的 是个意外
Yeah, we didn't mean to! That was an accident!
哈哈 我就知道会发生这种事
Ha ha, I knew this was gonna happen.
都是我们的错 对不起 克洛伊
Agh, it's all our fault. I'm so sorry, Chloe.
- 让我来帮帮忙 - 不用了
- Uh, let me help you. - It's okay.
不 请让我帮帮忙吧
No, please, let me help. Come on.
我说不用了 你们走吧
I said it's fine! Just go.
你们本来不就要走吗
You guys needed to leave anyways.
没关系的 你们好像有急事
It's okay. It seems like you guys are in a hurry.
别担心 熊熊们 我们会收拾好的
Don't worry, bears, we'll take care of it.
太对不起了
I'm so sorry.
我们非常抱歉
We're really sorry.
回头见 克洛伊
We'll see you later, Chloe.
圣诞快乐 你们这些肮脏的动物
Merry Christmas, you filthy animals!
约翰 闭嘴
John, quiet!
事情进行得不太顺利啊 棕熊
That didn't go so well, Grizz.
是啊 但是别担心 兄弟们
Yeah, but, hey, don't worry, guys.
总有意外的
Off parties happen!
而参加糯懦拉的派对 一切都值了
And Nom Nom's party is gonna be all worth it!
这太疯狂了
This is insane!
装饰太华丽了
The decor is out of this world!
白熊承认这很出色
Ice Bear admits impressiveness.
派对很燃
Party very flammable.
不敢相信我们可以参加
I can't believe we're even allowed to be here!
你们不能
You're not!
你们来这里干什么 熊们
What do you think you're doing here, bears?!
想来炫耀什么吗
Come to show me up again, huh?!
但你邀请了我们啊
But you invited us!
什么 我为什么要邀请你们
What!? Why would I invite you?
给我 随便吧
Give me that! Ugh, whatever.
很明显 这个邀请函不是给你们的
Clearly, this invitation was not meant for you.
- 这发错了 - 我的手机
- This was a mistake! - My phone!
喂 管社交的家伙 你被炒了
Hey, social media guy... You're fired!
还有你们 赶紧走
And you... get lost!
不要逼我来硬的 你们都得求着我...
Or I'll have you thrown out so hard, you'll be begging for...
- 呃 先生 - 怎么了
- Uh, sir? - What?
大家好啊
Oh. Hey, world,
我在这里和熊熊朋友们闲聊呢
I'm just here, chillin' with my pals, the bears.
在我的派对都玩得挺开心的 对吧
We're all having a dope time at my holiday bash, right, guys?
对着镜头笑一个
Smile for the cameras.
别忘了你们特别的礼物
Don't forget your super special gift...
是不是很棒
Isn't that great?!
现在快走
Now get lost!
来吧 让我们分享更多的快乐吧
Come, come, let us spread even more joy!
简直不敢相信
I can't believe
从朋友的派对匆匆忙忙离开 就为了这个
we rushed through our friends' parties... for this.
他们才是真正在乎我们的
They're the ones that really care about us.
我们这个圣诞节
We've been real dingles
做得太差了
this Christmas.
我猜那些派对都结束了吧
I bet those parties are all over now.
要是
If only, you know,
我们可以弥补一下就好了
we could make it up to them somehow.
兄弟们 我有一个主意
Guys, I have an idea!
好了 第一站是游骑兵站
All right! First stop is Tabes!
拯救圣诞节的时候到了
Time to fix Christmas!
来了 你们好
Coming! Hey there...
天啊 看看你这个小可爱
Oh, my gosh, look at you!
想一起玩耍吗
You want to play?!
来吧 好狗狗
Oh, come on, boy!
我们走 小游骑兵
Let's go, little ranger!
太棒了
Perfect!
那是什么味道
What is that?
克洛伊 你在做什么吃的吗
Chloe, were you making something?
不 不是我
No, it's not me.
哇 伙计们
Whoa! Guys?
呃 早上好
Oh, uh, good morning!
不好意思 我们昨晚匆忙离开
We're sorry we rushed out last night,
我们想弥补一下
and we wanted to make it up to you!
哇 看上去真棒啊
Wow! This looks amazing!
白熊特殊的友好赠品
Ice Bear's special peace offering.
我们知道这不代表昨天的事情没关系了
Uh, we know this doesn't right all the wrong we did yesterday,
我也知道从地毯里清理泡菜一点也不容易
and I'm sure it's very hard getting kimchi out of a carpet,
我们只是想让你知道 我们很在乎你的
and we just want to let you know we really care about you.
太好吃了
Mmm! It's so good.
姜和泡菜
The ginger and the kimchi! Oh!
还有孜然啊 别忘了蘸酱
There's cumin in there. Oh, don't forget the sauce.
那个不能少
Don't get cheated.